tigerclaw.com 2015-03-21

# Tiger Claw » Customer Service :: Martial Arts Supplies, Uniforms, Sparring Gear, and More

## Customer Service

## Privacy Policy

**What information do we collect?  
**When you establish a wholesale account with Tiger Claw, we will ask you for basic contact information to include; Business name, billing address, shipping address, contact phone numbers, owner name, proof of business, and other related information concerning your business.

**How do we use your information?  
**We may use the information we collect from you when you register for a wholesale account with Tiger Claw in the following ways:

  * To allow us to quickly respond to any of your customer service needs.
  * To quickly process your transactions.

**How do we protect visitor information?  
**Tiger Claw is very conscious of your individual and business security concerns. Therefore, we have implemented several security measures to safeguard your confidential personal and business information. Your business information is kept behind our secured network and is only accessible by a limited number of Tiger Claw staff that has special access rights to our network and customer information. The Tiger Claw staff is required to keep all of our client information confidential. When you place orders online or access your account information it is on our secure server. All confidential or sensitive information you supply is transmitted using Secure Socket Layer (SSL) technology. Your personal or business credit card information, if you have applied to pay for your transactions in that manner, is not kept on our Internet server. Your credit card information is kept on our internal system and only accessed by Tiger Claw staff members that have the proper access rights to your confidential information.

**Do we use "cookies"?  
**Yes. Considering that the Tiger Claw website can only be accessed by wholesale clients, it is necessary to use cookies to accomplish this task. A cookie is a small file that a site transfers to your computer’s hard drive through your Web browser. This enables our site to determine if you are logged into our wholesale only website and process the items that you place in our shopping cart. This keeps the general public from accessing Tiger Claw wholesale prices. This is necessary to allow our wholesale pricing to only be viewable by our wholesale clients.

By adjusting your browser settings, you can be warned each time a cookie is being sent to your computer or turn them completely off. If you turn your cookies off, you will not be able to login to the Tiger Claw website to place orders or check wholesale pricing. You can still place your orders over the telephone or via fax or email.

**Do we disclose the information we collect to outside parties?  
**Tiger Claw does not sell, trade, or transfer to outside parties any of your personal or confidential information. The term 'outside parties' does not include any our parent company, Pioneer Interstate, Inc.'s divisions - e.g.: Kung Fu Tai Chi Magazine.

**Can you remove or modify information you have provided to us?  
**Yes. You can at anytime request that your personal and/or business information be removed from the Tiger Claw website. Note that we will maintain your information in our internal computer system to service your transactions and for record keeping purposes. If you desire for all your information to be removed from our system (closing your account) please contact our customer service department at 1-800-821-5090.

**Third party links  
**Tiger Claw may include third party links on our website in an attempt to provide you with additional information. These linked sites will have separate and independent privacy polices. We have no responsibility or liability for the content and activities of any linked site. Tiger Claw seeks to protect the integrity of out site and welcomes any feedback concerning linked sites.

**Changes to our policy  
**If Tiger Claw decides to change our privacy policy, those changes will be posted on this page. Policy changes will only apply to any information collected after the posted date of the policy change. This privacy policy was last modified on December 20, 2006.

**Questions and feedback  
**Tiger Claw welcomes all questions, comments, and concerns about our privacy policy. Please send your query using the “Contact” button in the left-hand menu, available on any page.

**Your consent  
**By using our site, you consent to our privacy policy

## 

## Featuring the Founder of Shaolin Kenpo  
Great Grandmaster Ralph Castro  
Saturday, March 28, 2015  
12:00pm-2:30pm

### Shaolin Kenpo Martial Arts,  
69 Washington St., Daly City, CA 94014  
Seminar Info: 650-274-7714
